

MUHAMMAD DANIAL HAZIM BIN HAMDAN

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To become an experience and ethical employee whereas I will improve myself and present the good quality and attitude, capable of working in team for various organizations and also able to proceed the growth of company development plus to contribute for the society.

CONTACT

ADDRESS: Tkt 1, Blok 18, Flat PKNS,

Seksyen 7, 40000 Shah Alam, Selangor.

AGE : 26

PHONE NO: 012-5386495

EMAIL : danialhazim89.dh@gmail.com

COMPUTER SKILLS

- MICROSOFT WORD
- MICROSOFT EXCEL
- MICROSOFT POWER POINT
- CATIA
- SOLIDWORKS
- AUTOCAD
- ANSYS FLUENT

REFERENCE

PN. NOR MERLISA BT. ALI Lecturer of Mechanical Engineering, Mara University of Technology, (UITM) Shah Alam.

Tel: 012-3729255

EN. RAJA ALJEFRI SHAH RAJA DAUD Assistant Manager (R&D Department) UMW Advantech Sdn. Bhd. Tel: 012-3763450

EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN ENGINEERING (HONS) MECHANICAL . 2013-2016

 $Mara\ University\ of\ Technology,\ (UITM)\ Shah\ Alam$

CGPA: 2.74

DIPLOMA IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING. 2010-2013

Mara University of Technology, (UITM) Permatang Pauh

CGPA: 3.38

SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA (SPM). 2009

SM Sains Teluk Intan, Perak (SEMESTI)

5A 4B 1C

EXPERIENCE

GRADUATE ENHANCEMENT PROGRAMME (SL1M) – Assistant Engineer

UMW Advantech Sdn. Bhd. (5 September 2017- 29 December 2017)

- Successfully represent the engineer from R&D department in conducting Production Line Trial for filter element of Perodua Bezza 1.0 L
- Request for old part of air filter from warehouse and convert it to new part number as requested by customer.
- Assist the engineer and involved in making the Standard of Procedure (SOP) for a new production line which is runner regrind for the use of injection moulding.
- Successfully refabricated some charcoal canister with small adjustments as required by customer
- Successfully did stock take/check at warehouse.

CNC MILLING AND LATHE TRAINING (GENERATE PROGRAMME)

CIAST Seksyen 19, Shah Alam (10 Days)

- Learn and practice Computer Numeric Control (CNC) machine for both milling and lathe
- Discovered the differences between MAZAK controller and FANUC controller
- Learn how to use EDM Wirecut machine

ENGINEERING TRAINEE

JKR Cawangan Kejuruteraan Mekanikal, Shah Alam (28 June 2015 – 18 September 2015)

- Inspect the air conditioning, pumping and fire protection systems whether they are in good condition or not in government building.
- Ensure the maintenance of vehicles are always updated in evaluation form before and after inspection.
- Manage the project's file for every department as required by the Head of Department (HOD).
- Helping the engineer present the concept of solar air conditioning and also its specification

CASHIER, TICKET SELLER

Mega Cineplex Seberang Perai, Pulau Pinang (Nov 2012- Dec 2012)

- Cashier for food and beverages
- Movies ticket's seller
- Guarding the movie's entrance.